# **ANNA IOSEFO**

### TAIMANE.IOSEFO@GMAIL.COM | 808.319.6753

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Highly motivated and ambitious individual with over 5+ years helpdesk/technical experience. Seeking to obtain a technical position to enhance my leadership, technical and operation skills while applying the knowledge learned from past work and education experiences.

## **SOFT / TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Effective communicator
- Creative thinker and problem solver
- Works well under pressure and in a dynamic environment
- Works well individually and in groups
- Proficient in MS Office Suite

- Troubleshooting common technical issues
- Knowledgeable in common OS such as Windows, macOS and Linux
- In-depth knowledge of hardware and software

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

IT HELPDESK LEAD/TECHNICIAN, Computer Technical Services | Aug 2018 - present

- Provide IT support services to clients and work closely with helpdesk and technical teams
- Monitor multiple mailboxes, route calls appropriately to technical teams
- Manage help desk team and work order system; create accounts and provide access to technicians and clients
- Create, assign and escalate tickets to technicians and monitor for SLA violations
- Help manage in-house company projects and collaborate with contracted clients daily

IT HELPDESK LEAD/TECHNICIAN, Dixie State University | Sep 2015 - Jul 2018

- Assisted students, faculty and staff with common technical issues
- Monitored inbox and ticketing system; Escalated tickets to technicians or supervisors
- Multi-tasked between dispatch and helpdesk technician duties
- Helped troubleshoot technical issues and maintained printer maintenance

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

SECURITY+, COMPTIA | Sep 2020

## **EDUCATION**

CYBER SECURITY OPERATIONS & LEADERSHIP, University of San Diego | Aug 2018 - May 2020 COMPUTER & INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, Dixie State University | Jan 2015 - May 2018